Register of the Spartacist League of the U.S. records
Hoover Institution Archives
- International Affiliate Issuances, 1966-2008 (Boxes 12-13, 17-22)
  - Internal issuances, 1973-2003
    - Internal bulletins, 1973-2003
      - International Communist League (Fourth Internationalist), International Secretariat
        - No. 53, 2000 October (Box-folder 22: 4)
        - No. 54, 2001 December (Box-folder 22: 5)
        - No. 55, 2002 May (Box-folder 22: 6)
        - No. 56, 2003 January (Box-folder 22: 7)
  - Public issuances, 1966-2008
    - Declaration of Principles, 1998 (Box-folder 22: 8-9)
      Includes English, French, German, Japanese, Chinese, Greek, Indonesian, Italian, Polish, Portuguese, Russian, Tagalog, Turkish and Spanish versions.
    - Hate Trotskyism, Hate the Spartacists (Spartacist League/Britain bulletin), no. 1, 1990 (Box-folder 22: 10)
    - Hate Trotskyism, Hate the Spartacists (Spartacist South Africa bulletin), no. 1, 1998 (Box-folder 22: 11)
    - Espartaco, Vol. 1, no. 1 (October), no. 2 (December), no. 3 (February-March), 1966-1967 (Box-folder 13: 14)
      Spanish-language publication of the Spartacist League of the U.S.
    - Klassenkampf, no. 1 (May ), no. 2 (July), no. 3 (September), no. 4 (November), 1967 (Box-folder 13: 15)
      German-language publication of the Spartacist League of the U.S.
    - Pamphlets, 1967-2008
      - Leon Trotsky, el posadismo y Espartaco, 1967 (Box-folder 13: 16)
      - Tesis sobre las guerrillas, 1967 (Box-folder 13: 17)
      - Documents sur "l'affaire Varga": la lutte de la tendance spartaciste internationale pour une commission d'enquête impartiale, 1977 (Box-folder 13: 18)
        Publication of the Ligue trotskyste de France, French section of the international Spartacist tendency.
      - Mai 68: Révolution sabotée, 1988 (Box-folder 22: 12)
        Publication of the Ligue trotskyste de France.
      - Workers Power and the Irish Workers Group, 1990 (Box-folder 13: 19)
        Hate Trotskyism, Hate the Spartacists bulletin no. 1, publication of Spartacist Publications, London, and the Dublin Spartacist Youth Group.
      - Ireland: Workers to Power!, 1991 (Box-folder 13: 20)
        Publication of the Dublin Spartacist Youth Group and the International Communist League [Fourth Internationalist].
      - Militant Labour's Touching Faith in the Capitalist State, 1994 (Box-folder 13: 21)
        Publication of Spartacist Publications, London.
      - The Fight for a Revolutionary Vanguard Party: Polemics on the South African Left, 1997 (Box-folder 22: 13)
        Publication of the International Communist League [Fourth Internationalist].
      - The Logan Dossier, 2007 (Box-folder 22: 14)
      - The Development and Extension of Leon Trotsky's Theory of Permanent Revolution, 2008 (Box-folder 22: 15)
      - Chinese language publications (Box-folder 22: 16)